{
    "subject": "resource/Peymot",
    "predicate": "ontology/isPartOf",
    "object": "resource/Mazandaran_Province",
    "human_readable": "Peymot is part of Mazandaran Province.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9197831153869629,
            "question": "What province is Peymot part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9115071892738342,
            "question": "Is Peymot in a province?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9047263264656067,
            "question": "Which province includes Peymot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8689662218093872,
            "question": "To which province does Peymot belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8323074579238892,
            "question": "What is the name of the province that contains Peymot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8059070110321045,
            "question": "In what province can you find Peymot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6953881978988647,
            "question": "Where is Peymot located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6146889328956604,
            "question": "Is Mazandaran Province a region or a country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5583888292312622,
            "question": "What are some other cities in Mazandaran Province?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4507603049278259,
            "question": "Can you name any landmarks in Mazandaran Province?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Peymot is part of Mazandaran Province.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2099_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some other cities in Mazandaran Province?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2099_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Mazandaran Province a region or a country?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2099_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Peymot located?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2099_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2099_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2099_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2099_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2099_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2099_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2099_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2099_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2099_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2099_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2099_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nExplanation:\nThe context information contains text from Wikipedia about Peymot, a village in Mian Band Rural District, which is located in the Central District of Nur County, and this county is part of Mazandaran Province. Therefore, the statement that Peymot is part of Mazandaran Province is supported by the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the statement that \"Peymot is part of Mazandaran Province.\" Both document paths 5.txt and 4.txt provide this detail, confirming that Peymot is a village located within Mazandaran Province, Iran."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}